

Yurii Khvyshchuk

Senior Full Stack JavaScript Engineer

CONTACTS

Ukraine, Lviv

+38 093 434 25 31

yuriikhvyshchuk@gmail.com

ABOUT

I am a Full-Stack Developer with extensive knowledge of a modern technology stack for web development. I can build single-page applications using React frameworks. I also have experience in server-side development with Node.js (Express.js, Koa.js, Meteor), as well as in hybrid/mobile development with React Native and Cordova.

Being a self-driven and proactive person, I always try to come up with new ideas and approaches when working on projects.

LANGUAGES

 ${\sf Ukrainian-native}$

Russian - native

English – upper intermediate

JOB EXPERIENCE

United Software Solutions | August 2020 - Present

Senior JavaScript Developer

Teonica | November 2019 - August 2020

Lead Front End Developer

Ralabs | January 2018 - November 2019

Software engineer

Cursor Education | Mach 2018 - August 2021

Fronted education support, lecturer

PROJECTS HISTORY

Ultimate virtual event platform (2 months, present) *A platform for virtual events, webinars, conferences*

Role: Full stack engineer

Team: 10 team members

Stack: NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, Redis, React, Redux, Pug, JQuery,

Docker

Worldwide online shopping platform (1 year)

Online shopping platform based on microservice architecture

Role: Backend lead, Fullstack developer

Team: 15 team members

Stack: React, React Native, Redux, Express, CosmosDB, Algolia, Redis

Road traffic management system (3 months)

Platform for monitoring city road traffic

Role: Fullstack developer Team: 4 team members

Stack: React, Redux, Mapblox, Rechart, NodeJS, Express, Postgres,

Postgis, Knex, Docker, AWS Amplify

EDUCATION

PROJECTS HISTORY

Lviv Polytechnic National University

Master's degree

Information networks of communication

2018

Lviv Polytechnic National University

Bachelor's degree

Telecommunications

2017

Smart energy management system (3 months)

Platform for smart home energy management

Role: Frontend developer Team: 5 team members

Stack: React, Redux, Highcharts

Custom software for a CrossFit Gym (4 months)

This is web application for gym management that includes a CRM database for tracking customers profiles and a management system for

employees and coaches.

Role: Lead Frontend developer

Team: 4 team members

Stack: React, Mobx, typescript

Application for promoting ideas (4 months)

Mobile application for creating missions that solve the problems of users' citizens. They can create own solution or vote for existing. The main goal of the application is to promote impactful ideas.

Role: Mobile developer Team: 2 team members

Stack: React Native, Mobx, typescript

Communication platform for housing associations (5 months)

This is a scalable communication platform for housing associations and the central source of information for tenants regarding calamities, renovations, disruptions and other reports. In the event of a report, tenants are always quickly and fully informed.

Role: Frontend lead
Team: 5 team members

Stack: PWA, React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Redux-Persist, NodeJS, KOA

Application for cryptocurrency exchange (4 months)

This is a peer-to-peer marketplace that allows individuals to buy crypto directly from other people nearby and spend it at physical stores located on the map

Role: Frontend (mobile) developer

Team: 10+ team members

Stack: Cordova, React, Redux, Ether.js

Web platform for the media company (3 months)

This is a web platform for publishing and reading news.

Role: Frontend (mobile) developer

Team: 15 team members

Stack: Next.JS, React, Redux, Koa

PROJECTS HISTORY

Restaurant application (4 months)

Restaurant management PWA application that provides features like mobile detailed menu, QR-code based access, ratings

Role: CTO, Lead developer Team: 5 team members

Stack: Typescript, NodeJS, Routing-Controllers, React, Mobx, MongoDB

Educational platform (4 months)

This is a platform for teachers and students for learning languages in real-time $\begin{tabular}{ll} \hline \end{tabular}$

Role: Fullstack developer Team: 3 team members

Stack: Meteor, MongoDB, React, Redux